Right now, some companies are paying up
to € 10,000 for agents that can be
built in just a single afternoon. In
this video, I’m building an MVP live
from start to finish with Cloud Code,
and I’ll give you all the prompts to
replicate it. To build it, though, we
won't go about it randomly; we’ll use
the theory Andrei Karpathy talks about
when building with AI, constructing a
small company brain around this agent
that we can use for future automations.
If you're new to the channel, I’m Joe
, and with my AI agency, Gente Sei, we
provide consulting to companies ranging
from € 10,000 a month up to € 50
million a year, and I also have a
private community for entrepreneurs and
freelancers who want to apply AI to
their business or resell it to others.
That said, let's get started. Before we
go build the system, let me briefly
explain what the pattern described by
Karpathy is. Here, when we talk about
Karpathy, we are talking about what is
defined as our LLM wiki, which is
nothing more than the Obsidian brain
that you often see in some videos. This
is an example, and this is exactly what
we are going to build little by little,
and if you see here, all the notes are
connected to one another, and we have
this visual effect of having this head
or this interconnected brain. Now let's
see how what Karpathy described
actually works. So, the premise he
starts from is the following: when
people use AI, they keep re-explaining
everything in every chat, but we have
this new methodology that somehow
allows the AI to start creating its own
knowledge in markdown files that the AI
can then maintain on its own. So what
does that mean? If we go and read his
post, which was this—it was
essentially a hyper-viral post where,
as you see below, he detailed what I am
now going to describe to you. What does
it tell us? It tells us that this LLM
wiki has three main layers, or these
are its building blocks. The first are
the so-called raw sources, and in this
case, we are talking about meeting
transcripts, perhaps documents or
emails, which are read and, let's say,
not touched in any way; they are truly
raw. The second building block is a
wiki. This means that the concept this
infrastructure is based on is the
concept of atomic notes, which means
small notes that are linked and that
the AI gradually updates for our client
or for the task we are working on. An
example is that the AI could start
describing the client's sector,
logistics for our client, the budget
perhaps still to be defined, maybe we
didn't talk about it on the call, and
the next steps are the proposal.
Obviously, after this note, there will
be a set of other notes, which are the
ones you see here, where we might have
the call transcript, here we might have
the client information; and we can
therefore have all these small notes
interconnected with each other. And the
nice part is precisely, as you see in
this image, that the AI can ultimately
navigate and update them in complete
autonomy. The third part we are going
to see will be the schema, therefore a
set of rules that explain to us how the
wiki is organized, so how to navigate
the wiki and what operations the AI can
perform. What operations can it perform
? There are mainly three. The first is
an operation we define as ingest or
ingestion, which means that any new
material is ingested by the AI and is
updated thanks to the AI. The second
operation is the query operation. What
does that mean? That we can ask a
question to our company Brain or our
notes and the AI is able, through these
connections, to answer and find the
correct response. The third operation
the AI performs is an operation called
lint. Essentially, it means that the AI
is automatically able to check for
contradictions, clean up old data, and
manage orphaned notes. The premise is,
this infrastructure will be an
infrastructure that we will use and is
very, very good for personal knowledge.
The focus of all this is that the human
curates the sources and asks the
questions. It does the rest. And this
knowledge base, even for this demo,
works very well if you are a solo
founder. In case you are interested in
something a bit more structured, in the
community here we have a company Brain
course in which we will explain what a
company Brain is, how it is structured,
and how to scale these company brains
to a corporate context. What will allow
us, therefore, to use these LLMs and
build our company Brain, specifically
for us with our business. I will give
you the prompts for everything. This
will be the structure we are going to
use. We will have our company Brain for
which I will give you a mini prompt now
. We will then have our cloud.md which
represents the schema, so what I was
telling you before, one of the three
things that allows us to understand how
to navigate this company Brain. We will
have a first part of sources in which
we will have a first piece, and those
will be the reference sources we will
use. We'll have a client folder and
then the skill we'll build in this
specific video, which is proposal
generation, so an automation of quotes,
and we will use a service called Pandoc
. In here, we'll also see that we have
various files that are things generated
by the AI, which could be logs of what
we've done or an index that tells us
how the Company Brain is structured,
what's inside it, and so on. And the
offer.md file will be the one generated
thanks to Pandoc before it's converted
into a PDF and then sent to our client.
Here, we'll have the so-called live
ingest, so we'll actually put in one of
our transcripts. This transcript will
be broken down into these micro-notes,
and once it's broken down, we'll be
able to go into Obsidian, see that our
Company Brain is starting to populate,
and the AI will automatically update
both our index and our log. In other
words, we don't need to know what they
are for now; they are all things I will
provide you, and the AI will update
them completely autonomously. So, to
show you the difference between having
a system—a skill—within a Company
Brain or not, I want to paste the same
type of transcript into both and show
you the qualitative difference between
the two scripts, okay? And between the
two outputs. Hey, please generate a
proposal for this client. You see,
there's nothing here. Let's give Claude
absolute freedom to do it, and here we
do the exact same thing. I'll show you
the output level now, what happens when
both systems finish. And these are the
two results. Now let me open them
quickly. The first is a Claude artifact
. See? In this case, yeah, guys,
there's no logo of mine, there's
nothing; it's something quite anonymous
, I'd almost call it AI slop. At this
point, as you can clearly see, we have
this objective, a system—so without
our Company Brain and a skill—leaving
everything generic, it doesn't even
have our logo. If we were to go back
inside this one and press down here,
where to find it, it would open
Pandadoc, and here, obviously, we now
have a totally different proposal. So,
you see, there's my logo, my company's,
an acquisition system for my client.
You see here that it briefly describes
the client's situation, the system we
are going to build, which will be lead
enrichment, based on the transcript
call you'll see later that I will give
you. so that you can use it. You can
see that it created the two options
with the available payment methods and
payment types, but not only that, we
now also have the possibility to send
it automatically and have both the
signature and payment handled through
Pandooc. So you can clearly understand
the difference in quality, both from an
aesthetic point of view and a
functional one. Let's start building
our Company Brain, and here you will
have a Notion page—I'll leave it
below—with all the prompts we are
going to use. So the first thing we do
is provide this prompt, which does
exactly what we just described for our
Company Brain. So what we will do is
copy this prompt, and then we need to
download Cloud Code. You decide where
you want to do it. You can do it in
Antigravity, so put Antigravity IDE
here, or you can do it within Cloud
Code, the desktop app. For the moment,
I will do it in here, but it makes
absolutely no difference. In here, we
have an empty folder that we will open,
and you can see it is completely empty.
How do we install Cloud Code in here?
We go to extensions and search for
Cloud. Sorry, Cloud Code. We will click
here and hit install. Once that's done,
you will have this gear icon in the top
right, and you can get in here. So,
what do we do? We go here and start by
entering the first prompt. This is a
prompt written, of course, with HTML
syntax, and what our prompt will do is
create this Company Brain structure,
just as we described before, with
everything it needs to contain, a
template, and completion criteria. And
in this case, I'm telling it, "Hey, for
any information you might not know,
feel free to use placeholders." Because
, in this case, I am doing a YouTube
demo and you can fill in the
information with demo content. My name
is Giovanni, my company is called Gente
Sei. Feel free to invent the rest; we
also offer lead generation services,
and we will do an example of that.
Perfect. In this case, as you saw
before, you will have a kind of
questionnaire that will ask you who you
are, what you do, and how you operate.
And in this case, I simply told it, "
Please create it for me," and then
populate this part with demo
information so that I can show you
exactly how the whole build works.
While our prompt finishes, I'll briefly
explain what type of flow we are going
to create. So, we want to create this
company Brain, and we want this company
Brain to have a skill that, in this
case, automates quotes because it makes
it much easier for us, right? Because
at that point, we wouldn't have to keep
providing a ton of information about
our company in every single prompt. We
could simply tell it to make a quote
for that client, and the AI will
automatically know exactly what
information to pull and where to get it
from. So, from a business perspective,
what kind of flow do we have? First of
all, we have a source. In this case,
we'll have a call transcript that goes
into our AI. You have the transcript in
Notion, we'll copy it, but here you can
decide, once this workflow is built, to
connect it to your note-taker like
Fathom or Fireflies. Then we'll have
the second step, which is the brain;
Claude designs the entire flow,
transforms the call we had into various
notes, and will then break it down into
pieces until it understands the
specific offer to use within PandaDoc
for the system. PandaDoc, on the other
hand, will produce—and now I'll show
you what it is—a signable document;
so, Claude writes here, and we'll have
the ability to sign, pay, and sign
directly within this document that will
reach our client, and then everything
will be saved in the memory as a
proposal. In case you didn't know it,
this service is called PandaDoc. Just
do it like this, I'll leave a link
below, you get 14 days free if you want
to use it. This is the system we are
going to use and. If you are interested
in understanding how I made this type
of template, etc., I made a fairly long
course in the introduction section,
after my 4-hour Claude for AI course;
inside here, you'll have the whole part
on how to make automatic quotes and a
walkthrough of PandaDoc. Actually, I
spent about thirty minutes here
explaining it in detail. Basically, I
still want to show you what's inside in
this video and. This is an excellent
system because this is a template I
prepared, complete with company logo,
collaboration proposal, and the
services we offer. And you see down
here, and after you see this is done
with my brand setup and brand
guidelines, we'll see that in the call
we'll have something like this; however
, all of this is populated
automatically with AI and we also have
the possibility of having a digital
signature. As you can see, in this case
, the signer is Marco Rossi. When we
send everything, PandaDoc will
automatically use this to have the
document signed. We could put the date
here, or it can also happen
automatically. So, this entire service
allows you to generate automatic
proposals with AI, starting from
templates like this and using so-called
dynamic variables or text fields. To
show you how it works, you just drag
one inside here, and then you can start
writing custom variables or have the AI
populate them. Okay? So this is just to
show you how it works. For this video,
I have already prepared the template,
and this is exactly what we are going
to use and what we want to automate. To
do it yourself, just go in here and you
can start playing around with the
various variables. Perfect, so in this
case, our skill is finished. We said
the brain structure was created, what's
in there? Empty, raw state, skills,
placeholders for you, for offers,
sources, and so on. So now we open a
new chat, we have done everything we
wanted, and our folder has been created
, and our company Brain can start
taking shape. Then we go into Notion,
and the first thing we need to do is
tell it to generate a skill with
PandaDoc. In this case, we will copy
the prompt, we will go here to paste it
, and what we will tell it now is,
please use the PandaDoc at this URL and
then this template. So, we will paste
our URL here. Perfect. And we will also
paste our screenshot. Here we are. One
thing missing is, of course, having the
API keys, which you can easily access.
So, even with the free version, go to
account at the bottom left, then you
have API and integrations here. If you
scroll all the way down to API and
Webhooks, you can open it, and here you
will have the ability to copy your API
keys and then paste them into Claude.
In this case, I just did it, copied it
into the file. And the thing we can do
now is tell it to bypass permission.
What it will do now is create our skill
, and then we can start testing it. Let
me explain how this integration works.
When we go to paste the transcript that
we now have in our Notion into Claude,
what it will do is break everything
into notes; the PandaDoc skill will
have three layers, it will have a first
script.py in which it creates, reads
the draft, and waits. Then it will go
on to create the proposal. It is
actually made with our template, and
once that is done, this is how we will
activate the skill. Again, for those of
you who don't know, a skill is just a
way of telling the cloud to automate
this workflow because the steps are
always the same, and so we have
automated a small piece of the process.
Perfect, now this was successful. You
see that it generated my scripts for my
generate proposal, and we now have our
skill.md with everything inside needed
to generate the proposal on PandaDoc.
What will we do now? We are going to
take the transcript of our call into
our PandaDoc and see if this actually
works. So let's copy it. This was a
discovery call for Rossi Marketing, and
now we will simply copy it, paste it,
and say something like this. Hey, um,
this is my call transcript. Please,
with the generate proposal skill,
generate a proposal for me that I can
send to my client. Ok, it says proposal
made, summary, document found, so let's
go open it. And here is what we get
again with our Mario Rossi. Um, here we
have the updated date, situation with
enrichment, infrastructure, copy, we
see that the price list has basically
been maintained. And now we have these
next steps and then we have the
signature. You see here it's slightly
modified. And now to see if this is
effectively what we discussed in the
call, let's go into our cloud source.
Here we should have our call already
put in the raw data, and we see there
are two ways to pay for it, same
identical system. The first is the
standard option, uh fixed cost, €
1000 setup, one-time which covers the
infrastructure, leadify extraction,
cloud enrichment, then a € 500
monthly retainer, and the second is the
performance option, setup reduced to
€ 600, and then € 80 for each
meeting. So, here we have, as you can
see, the one-time setup and here we
have the 2-month retainer, so 1000 plus
the 500 for 2 months, and then we have
the performance setup instead with €
80 per meeting. So from here we see
that everything worked correctly. Now
that we've seen how to build these
offers, let's look quickly at what many
people get wrong, which is how to price
them. So, the two pricing methods we
have to start observing this slide are
pricing based on what our cost is to
produce it or pricing based on the
value that this type of automation, so
proposal automation within a company
brain, can generate. An important
premise is that this type of automation
can have substantial value because, for
example, an 8-hour one-day training on
AI can cost 10,000 to 15,000. An
automation like this can cost as much
as € 10,000. Will it be the first one
you sell? Absolutely not. But now I
want to explain the theoretical concept
that allows you to start raising your
price and also adapting your avatar to
your offer. If you price these
automations based on cost, objectively
these automations require a fairly low
cost to build, because we're talking
about a subscription likely for 100 or
$ 200 for cloud and then an automation
that we can do with, if I'm not
mistaken, $ 59 for PandaDoc plus a
couple of other things. So cost-based
is a strategy that will make you lose
and will increasingly squeeze your
margins. If you fail to position an
offer in a way that explains to the
client the value you bring. This other
pricing methodology is a methodology
called value-based pricing, and
therefore it is based on the value you
will generate for a company. How do we
calculate this value? Well, value can
be seen as the time, in this case, that
the company is saving by automating
their proposal generation process;
therefore, in this case, it is the time
a person takes to make a proposal; so,
time per person per proposal, we can
multiply that by the number of
proposals per month. This is a proxy.
If you want to go into detail on how I
build this price list, you can go to my
community; we have a specific course on
how to price offers and how to resell
them, but this is a start. Then the
second additional method—so it's not
an "or," but an "and"—is the ROI part
, meaning let's assume this person is
saving a total of maybe 10 hours a
month creating these proposals. How
does this translate into value for the
company? So, if this person were to use
these 10 hours and maybe land two
clients in those 10 hours, how much
upside could this bring in terms of
revenue? And so this is what you get—
we're using random numbers here, but
let's assume an average client for you
is 2,500, so maybe two clients and
therefore 10 hours are worth € 5,000
to you. These are, of course, monthly,
so you can already see that just by
showing what—and here we would
obviously need to multiply it by the
hourly rate we pay the person—you can
see that with a few simple calculations
, though very much simplified, it’s
quite easy to start valuing this
automation at € 6,000 per month.
Obviously, you need a business that
needs it, you need a market that allows
for it, and you need an avatar willing
to pay; so you have to be skilled,
because there are different ways to
create these types of automations, and
scaling them isn't as simple as doing
them one-shot. But you can see that
this is the method, and here we are
looking at how many days you actually
save compared to the time it will take
the system to generate all the
proposals you want. And so, you can see
these are prices you can consider
entry-level, so you can start offering
this automation—after having done a
few, of course—between € 1,000 and
€ 5,000, and then you can have a
retainer if the company needs this
automation to be maintained. For
example: it could be for people who
have very large quotes, perhaps
companies selling heavy machinery,
where they sell in the English market,
the Italian market, the French or
German market, and so these automations
start to require different languages,
but above all, they may need to take
different forms depending on the type
of machinery. You can clearly see that
a retainer will obviously be needed
here. Please, one last thing I want to
emphasize once again: price based on
value and not based on the hours you
spend developing, because otherwise
your margins will go down and no
successful company ever prices at cost.
And so there it is, an agent that, if
implemented correctly, companies are
willing to pay thousands of euros for.
Building it as an MVP, as in this case,
is simple. If you want to go deeper and
want a comprehensive course on how to
build these things with Cloud Code,
join the community and you’ll find
everything there.